Quickly
understand this, a big news was published in India
that
[Music]
Yogi
Adityanath Ajay
subscribe
subscribe to your mind
friends I am Girti and
welcome to our channel so friends
subscribe to channel 100 do subscribe to the channel
subscribe to our channel
so coming to the topic, there was a
lot of discussion about what happened in UP that
Gandhi has been arrested and
after this everything was on Yogi, that is, who is
harassing the opposition, so our
neighbor Pakistan also discussed about this and you
can see this mark and
if he becomes the Prime Minister then what should be done, so regarding this regarding the
industry in this video of Pakistan
we have also
understood this in India
[Music]
that he was also arrested in the quadrilateral
and along with him the secretary
secretary was
appointed there
first
Mumbai,
Kolkata
and but some
more were appointed so
click on Yogi Adityanath
Salman do
not forget to subscribe
friends in the video you said
about Pakistan and such a secretary and the government of life
is very good but that bastard
now let us come to the side of the Governor
I will not talk about Yogi ji etc.  I am telling you about the state,
before Jogi, the people of the country were protesting
but when Jogi came to power, in this four
years itself, the GDP growth of UP has increased
from 10 lakh crores to 21 lakh crores
and the growth which was online has come down from 70%
to 4.1% now, so if we
look at it economically, then this is a very remarkable
development and if we go
towards the definition of what to do, then all the countries should
define vaccination, then UP is the first state to
give the highest pension of 33 lakhs in a day,
giving political benefits to 80, Rajesh Jain has
become the state giving the highest vaccination, so this is also a
very big result in itself and if you
look at the criminal record, then you must be seeing on criminal every day
that someone or the other from UP gets
arrested or they are sitting there with illegal occupation,
that too goes to some extent, all this happened, so
this three years development happened and then it became an option
and then it became a criminal and corruption  It has become
equal to whoever, whoever there is
corruption, they
put the situation or vigilance on him, so
you know about corruption also, so if apart from this, what
they said that we have changed the names of all these places,
we have not changed the names of the places, we are
saying that the names of the places were there earlier, if you see,
you will see that who was the owner of your father,
he will bring it and if you want to
buy the land then will
you keep the name of that land which was bought earlier, now you will take it in the
name of someone else, so such things, the Mughals who
came, he was our second, we changed his name,
then if we change the name Hiraman during our rule or
not, it depends on our blood, this is done
in Pakistan, so this is the situation,
we can take as many names as we want,
whoever changes that name, soon we
mean the earlier name should remain Namdev and
if you know there, when a riot
breaks out, there is
politics there, so if this experiment is not done then
you get traffic jam on the road, which
means the government
goods of our people are
used, then the police
means for the skin police  There is a lot to pick up from the laundry
and this is happening while we are here, so
if we do it or not, and it has happened
and
I have subscribed, there is an election, so all these
people should do this there and
show their political power, everyone
knows who is not doing good work for us, so he must be doing
good work, it does
not mean that whatever your government does
and will do, and about what happened,
if he also climbed on the car
and after that, which
means and there was a lot of fuel from both sides, that is
not for them, and
they beat him to death in front of the police,
but then
some experienced face came forward, so this
whole issue and whatever it is, we are saying that if he will be the
Prime Minister in 2014, then whatever happens will be
seen, but the one who does
development from the heart, he will go and become the Prime
Minister in future, like Mukherjee Jogi completed his team time
and left Gujarat for a lot of development, then
he became the Prime Minister and on
Sunday, here he is doing development,
he played well and is a good man, so
if such an opportunity is given, it may be in 2036 or
29th then going ahead, that
means death has not even happened that much, it means a lot, so
why could it not be made, it can be made till
2036, we cannot go without it, but
why not, we are doing development
and whatever is there, we are doing good work, so
friends, that's all in this video, whatever you
bring, and Pakistan
one and a half and you must like the video and you
should because
we are close to Shravan, if you subscribe, we will
reach you in a day or two,
thank you, we will meet soon in a new
video in Hindi